[
    {
        "front": "うし",
        "back": "牛 \nCow",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "うま",
        "back": "馬 \nHorse",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "さかな",
        "back": "魚 \nFish",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "かい",
        "back": "貝 \nShellfish",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "あめ",
        "back": "雨 \nRain",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "てん",
        "back": "天 \nHeaven",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんき",
        "back": "気 \nWeather",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "にんき",
        "back": "人気 \nPopularity",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "きをつける",
        "back": "気をつける \nTo take care",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "くるま",
        "back": "車 \nCar",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんしゃ",
        "back": "電車 \nTrain",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "もん",
        "back": "門 \nGate",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごぜん",
        "back": "午前 \n(In the) morning",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごご",
        "back": "午後 \n(In the) afternoon",
        "chapter": "N5 K7"
    }
]